

PROFILE

Web developer with a background in management and intellectual property law. Highly organised and valued team member with great interpersonal skills. Experienced at working under pressure to meet deadlines, and adept at finding technical solutions to problems.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript (ES6
- HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstran
- Responsive Design
- React, React Native, Redux
- Angular, Vue
- :• Node.is
- APIs
- AWS
- MongoDB, SQL, Firebase
- Git, Branching
- TDD (Jest, Cucumber)
- Chrome Dev Tools
- Postman
- Android Studio

Languages

- English (native)
- German (B1)

CONTACT ME

Phone: 0049-178-6820851

Email: ianflemingdeveloper@gmail.com

Address: Nawiaskystr. 18, 81735 Munich

Website: www.ianflemingdeveloper.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/i-fleming/

GitHub: github.com/ianfleming464/

Music: ian-fleming.bandcamp.com,



IAN FLEMING

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Formalprozessabteilung Sachbearbeiter / Legal Assistant

Grünecker Patent- und Rechtsanswälte, Munich: May 2019-present

- Responsible for all formal processes related to European Community and foreign designs, foreign trademarks: reporting on publication/registration, invoicing, monitoring deferment deadlines, fee payment, ensuring accuracy and attention to detail.
- Fully-digitised the fee payment/deferment schedule, in order to make it legible and understandable, and ensure no deadlines are missed in the event of absence.

Bar manager

The Keg Bar, Munich: March 2015 - March 2017

- Employed an analytical mindset to ensure everything ran smoothly: organised staff and delegated work, meticulously planned drink/food orders depending on demand/upcoming events, created an extensive electronic staff handbook detailing every aspect of the job (from how to pour every drink/cocktail on the menu to how to deal with electrical faults in the building).

Book department worker, duty/weekend manager

The Book Centre, Waterford, Ireland: August 2008 - June 2014

- Ordered books for ca. 8 different sections, ensuring we always had exactly what the customer wanted before they even knew they wanted it.
- Aggregated different rare title websites, so that we could safely say that, no matter how obscure or long out of print a title is, we could generally source it at a reasonable price.

EDUCATION

Career Foundry

Full-Stack Development Certificate, January 2020 - November 2020

- Intensive project-based course building apps using a variety of technologies, under the guidance of industry-leading tutor and mentor.
- Utilised a diverse range of APIs for apps, such as a Meetup events app and a Pokedex clone.
- Coded a fully-functional React Native chat app for Android and IOS.
- Created an entire full-stack movie app with login and user account functionality, using the MERN stack.

University College Limerick, Ireland

MA in Music Technology, 2012-2013

- Graduated with a 1.1
- Wrote a peer-reviewed scientific paper on a piece of music I created and released, based on the voice of author Harlan Ellison ('I Have No Mouth (pts. 1-6) Introducing Postdigital Spectralism' Leonardo Music Journal LMJ24 p.45-48, Dec 2014 www.mitpressjournals.org/doi/abs/10.1162/LMJ_a_00201)

University College Cork, Ireland

BA in English and Sociology, 2000-2003